{
  "q1": {
    "question": "Who teaches Harry how to play Wizard’s chess?",
    "choices": [
      "A) Hagrid",
      "B) Hermione",
      "C) Ron",
      "D) Dudley"
    ],
    "answer": "2"
  },
  "q2": {
    "question": "When is Harry Potter’s birthday?",
    "choices": [
      "A) December 31",
      "B) June 31",
      "C) July 31",
      "D) August 31"
    ],
    "answer": "2"
  },
  "q3": {
    "question": "Who teaches History of Magic at Hogwarts?",
    "choices": [
      "A) Professor Flitwick",
      "B) Professor Sprout",
      "C) Professor Vector",
      "D) Professor Binns"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  "q4": {
    "question": "Who was not at the Dursley’s the night Harry’s parents died?",
    "choices": [
      "A) Albus Dumbledore",
      "B) Sirius Black",
      "C) Rubeus Hagrid",
      "D) Minerva McGonagall"
    ],
    "answer": "1"
  },
  "q5": {
    "question": "Who said this?: 'I am good looking enough for both of us.'",
    "choices": [
      "A) Draco Malfoy",
      "B) Ron Weasley",
      "C) Ginny Weasley",
      "D) Fleur Delacour"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  "q6": {
    "question": "Which of these spells is an Unforgivable Curse?",
    "choices": [
      "A) Sectumsempra",
      "B) Crucio",
      "C) Expecto Patronum",
      "D) Stupefy"
    ],
    "answer": "1"
  },
  "q7": {
    "question": "Who said this?: 'It’s Levi-o-sa, not Levio-sa.'",
    "choices": [
      "A) Harry Potter",
      "B) Gilderoy Lockhart",
      "C) Petunia Dursley",
      "D) Hermione Granger"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  "q8": {
    "question": "Which of the following is not a trait of Slytherin house?",
    "choices": [
      "A) Determination",
      "B) Cunning",
      "C) Ambition",
      "D) Wit"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  "q9": {
    "question": "Which animal does Hermione become when she takes Polyjuice Potion in Chamber of Secrets?",
    "choices": [
      "A) A toad",
      "B) A cat",
      "C) A rat",
      "D) An owl"
    ],
    "answer": "1"
  },
  "q10": {
    "question": "Which of these spells will summon an object to you?",
    "choices": [
      "A) Expelliarmus",
      "B) Wingardium Leviosa",
      "C) Accio",
      "D) Lumos"
    ],
    "answer": "2"
  }
}{
  "q1": {
    "question": "Who teaches Harry how to play Wizard’s chess?",
    "choices": [
      "A) Hagrid",
      "B) Hermione",
      "C) Ron",
      "D) Dudley"
    ],
    "answer": "2"
  },
  "q2": {
    "question": "When is Harry Potter’s birthday?",
    "choices": [
      "A) December 31",
      "B) June 31",
      "C) July 31",
      "D) August 31"
    ],
    "answer": "2"
  },
  "q3": {
    "question": "Who teaches History of Magic at Hogwarts?",
    "choices": [
      "A) Professor Flitwick",
      "B) Professor Sprout",
      "C) Professor Vector",
      "D) Professor Binns"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  "q4": {
    "question": "Who was not at the Dursley’s the night Harry’s parents died?",
    "choices": [
      "A) Albus Dumbledore",
      "B) Sirius Black",
      "C) Rubeus Hagrid",
      "D) Minerva McGonagall"
    ],
    "answer": "1"
  },
  "q5": {
    "question": "Who said this?: 'I am good looking enough for both of us.'",
    "choices": [
      "A) Draco Malfoy",
      "B) Ron Weasley",
      "C) Ginny Weasley",
      "D) Fleur Delacour"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  "q6": {
    "question": "Which of these spells is an Unforgivable Curse?",
    "choices": [
      "A) Sectumsempra",
      "B) Crucio",
      "C) Expecto Patronum",
      "D) Stupefy"
    ],
    "answer": "1"
  },
  "q7": {
    "question": "Who said this?: 'It’s Levi-o-sa, not Levio-sa.'",
    "choices": [
      "A) Harry Potter",
      "B) Gilderoy Lockhart",
      "C) Petunia Dursley",
      "D) Hermione Granger"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  "q8": {
    "question": "Which of the following is not a trait of Slytherin house?",
    "choices": [
      "A) Determination",
      "B) Cunning",
      "C) Ambition",
      "D) Wit"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  "q9": {
    "question": "Which animal does Hermione become when she takes Polyjuice Potion in Chamber of Secrets?",
    "choices": [
      "A) A toad",
      "B) A cat",
      "C) A rat",
      "D) An owl"
    ],
    "answer": "1"
  },
  "q10": {
    "question": "Which of these spells will summon an object to you?",
    "choices": [
      "A) Expelliarmus",
      "B) Wingardium Leviosa",
      "C) Accio",
      "D) Lumos"
    ],
    "answer": "2"
  }
}
